engineeradebtfreelife.com 2016-11-20

# Disclosure policy, Terms & Conditions, Privacy Policy - Coupons and Freebies Mom

[](http://www.couponsandfreebiesmom.com/grouponbodyshop)[](http://www.couponsandfreebiesmom.com/link/ebayfashionvault)[](http://www.disclosurepolicy.org/)_These policies are valid starting April 25, 2008 & were last updated September 29, 2016. _

Disclosure policy:

This blog is a collaborative blog written by two individuals. For questions about this blog or for advertising information, please contact mom AT couponsandfreebiesmom DOT com.

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions, and/or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

Coupons and Freebies Mom, LLC, is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com

The owner(s) of this blog may be compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog may receive compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog may contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content may not always be identified.

The rules for all giveaways on this website shall be determined solely by this blog. Giveaway winners must have a valid United States mailing address and provide the address if asked.

Unless otherwise expressly stated, you should assume that Coupons and Freebies Mom, LLC has an affiliate relationship or other material connection to the providers of goods and services mentioned by, recommended, hyperlinked to, or otherwise referenced on Coupons and Freebies Mom, LLC. In addition, you should assume that Coupons and Freebies Mom, LLC may be compensated monetarily or non-monetarily when you visit, purchase goods or services from, or take any other action on a third-party website mentioned by, recommended, hyperlinked to, or otherwise referenced on Coupons and Freebies Mom, LLC. You should always perform due diligence before buying any goods or services online or offline.

To get your own policy, go to [http://www.disclosurepolicy.org](http://www.disclosurepolicy.org/)

**Coupons and Freebies Mom website terms & conditions:**

Limitation of liability:

Your use of this web site is at your own risk. The materials on this web site are provided “as is”. Coupons and Freebies Mom will not be liable under any circumstances to you for damages or losses resulting from your use of, misuse of, or reliance on the website, or on the web site content, or any events beyond the reasonable control of Coupons and Freebies Mom.

You may be transferred to third party websites through links on this site. Use of any linked web site is at the user’s own risk. Coupons and Freebies Mom is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. Your correspondence or activities with third parties are between you and the third party only. You agree that Coupons and Freebies Mom, LLC, will not be responsible or liable for losses or damages resulting from transactions with third parties.  Coupons and Freebies Mom does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.

IN NO EVENT SHALL COUPONS AND FREEBIES MOM, LLC, AND ANY SUBSIDIARIES, EMPLOYEES OR SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, WHETHER DIRECT, INDIRECT, GENERAL, SPECIAL, COMPENSATORY, CONSEQUENTIAL, AND/OR INCIDENTAL, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE CONDUCT OF YOU (OR ANYONE) IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THE SITE, SERVICES, OR THESE TERMS OF USE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, BODILY INJURY, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, OR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. THIS LIABILITY LIMIT APPLIES EVEN IF COUPONS AND FREEBIES MOM, LLC OR A THIRD-PARTY ACTED NEGLIGENTLY.

**Privacy Policy**

Log Files

Like most standard websites, this website uses log files. These include: Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Web Cookies

Web cookies (also known as HTTP cookies, or just cookies) are parcels of text that are sent by a server to a Web browser, and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. In other words, a cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s computer that is tied to information about the user.

This website does use cookies. Additionally, some of my business partners (for example, advertisers) may use cookies as well. This site has no access to, or control of advertisers’ web cookies.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. Please check your browser’s help section for instructions on how to do this.

Links

This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. I encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy policy (or privacy statement) of each and every website you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.

Advertisers

I use outside advertising networks and companies in order to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons in order to collect data in the ad serving process. These such cookies and/or web beacons are collected by the companies and/or advertising networks, themselves. I do not have any access to this information.

I currently work with several advertising networks and companies, such as: AdThrive, Adsense & others. If you have any questions, please check their websites for their respective privacy policies.

Amendment:

Coupons and Freebies Mom, LLC, reserves the right, in its discretion, to amend this Agreement at any time by posting amendments on the website. You are responsible for periodically reviewing the amendments, and you are deemed to be aware of such amendments. If you do not agree to the amended terms and conditions, your only choice is to immediately stop using the website.

Notice Regarding Interest-Based Advertising Partner Websites may allow third-party companies, including ad networks, to serve advertisements, provide other advertising services and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. Third party companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visit to this website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. Third party may use non- cookie technologies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity including your activities on this website. These technologies may be used directly on this website. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these non-cookie technologies, and those browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on such techniques. To learn more about this Interest-Based Advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising by those third parties that are members of self-regulatory programs such as the Network Advertising Initiative, please visit the NAI’s website ([http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)) which will allow you to opt out of Interest-Based Advertising by one, or all, NAI members.

Third parties, including Facebook, may use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from our website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. You can opt-out of the collection and use of information for ad targeting. To exercise such choice, visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.aboutads.info%2Fchoices&h=IAQGiuNCY&s=1) and <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please feel free to email mom (at) couponsandfreebiesmom (dot) com.

Privacy policy adapted from [Aaron Cook](http://www.aaroncook.com/2008/03/sample-website-privacy-policy-you-can.html).
